[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Lost Boys, the Frog Brothers convince Sam that the only way to help Michael would be to stake him in the heart and kill him.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Apocalypse Now, directed by Roger Corman, was released in 1979.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Experiments prove that men are usually better at decoding facial expressions than women.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The color byzantium is a shade of this color.", "correct_answer": "Purple", "incorrect_answers": ["Brown", "Green", "Black"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of fish is Nemo from the 2003 animated film Finding Nemo?", "correct_answer": "Clownfish", "incorrect_answers": ["Butterfly fish", "Moonfish", "regal tang"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What cat breed, also called the Greyhound of the cats, has no hair except for down?", "correct_answer": "Cornish Rex", "incorrect_answers": ["Don Sphynx", "Oriental Bicolour", "Sokoke"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is certainly feasible to practice medicine without ever prescribing opiate medications.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was the Clydesdale Horse Society formally founded?", "correct_answer": "1887", "incorrect_answers": ["1925", "1901", "1885"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term refers to a phobia that involves fear of men?", "correct_answer": "Arrhenphobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Botophobia", "Xenophobia", "Nosophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the apple tree?", "correct_answer": "Its crown is broad and dense.", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "It is evergreen.", "It grows up to 60 feet (18 meters)."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of the most basic characteristics of our memory is the ability to forget, which is considered to be this type of function.", "correct_answer": "Adaptive function", "incorrect_answers": ["Developing function", "Cognitive function", "Protective function"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who won an Academy Award as the director of Forrest Gump?", "correct_answer": "Robert Zemeckis", "incorrect_answers": ["Stephen Spielberg", "Ron Howard", "Rob Reiner"]}]